{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Rendering in React",
      "description": "React's component structure allows for quickly building a complex web application that relies on DOM manipulation. "
    },
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application.",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "Mock Deck 3",
      "description": "MD",
      "id": 8
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "front": "Differentiate between Real DOM and Virtual DOM.cgvcvcv",
      "back": "Virtual DOM updates are faster but do not directly update the HTMLcvcvcvcv"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "front": "How do you modify the state of a different React component?cvcvcv",
      "back": "Not at all! State is visible to the component only.cvcvcvcv"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "front": "How do you pass data 'down' to a React child component?xcvxcv",
      "back": "As properties or propsxcvxcvxcv"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "front": "What path will match the follow Route?asdasdasdasda\n<Route>\n  <NotFound />\n</Route>",
      "back": "All paths. A route with no path matches all URL's"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "front": "What does <Switchasdasdasdasdasdasdasd> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> "
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "front": "bqweqwe",
      "back": "bqweqweqwe"
    },
    {
      "front": "What has ears but cannot hear?",
      "back": "A cornfield",
      "deckId": 8,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "front": "qweqweqweqweqw",
      "back": "qweqweqweqweeqweqwe"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "front": "qweqweqsdfsdfsdfsdf",
      "back": "weqweqwesdfsdfsdf"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "front": "sdfsdfsdfsdf",
      "back": "sdfsdfsdfsdfsdfsdf"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "front": "sdfsdfsdsdfsdf",
      "back": "fsdfsdfsdsdfsdfsdf"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "front": "sdfsdfsdf",
      "back": "sdfsdfsdf"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "front": "fsdfsdfssdfsdfsdf",
      "back": "dfsdfsdfsdsdfsdfsdf"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "front": "sdfsdfscxxvxcvxc",
      "back": "dfsdfsdcvxcvxcv"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "front": "sdfsdfsd",
      "back": "fsdfsdf"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "front": "xcvxcvxcv",
      "back": "xcvxcvxcv"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "front": "",
      "back": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "front": "dafasdfadfgdfgdf",
      "back": "dsfasdfasdfasdfgdfgdfg"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "front": "sdf",
      "back": "sdf",
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "front": "5",
      "back": "4",
      "deckId": "1"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "front": "4",
      "back": "6",
      "deckId": "1"
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "front": "asdasdaIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIII",
      "back": "sdasdasdasdasdasdIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIII",
      "deckId": "1"
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "front": "sdasdasdasddsfsdfs",
      "back": "asdasdasdasdassdfsdfsdfs",
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "front": "sdfsdfsd",
      "back": "fsdfsdfsdf",
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "",
      "back": "",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 25
    },
    {
      "front": "asdasdasd",
      "back": "asdasdasdasd",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 26
    },
    {
      "front": "I hate this",
      "back": "I haet everything",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 27
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "front": "yhtyutyutyudrwerwer",
      "back": "tyutyutyutyuwerwerwe",
      "deckId": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "front": "tyutyutywerwerwerwerwer",
      "back": "utyutyutyutyutyuwerwerwerwerwer",
      "deckId": 2
    },
    {
      "front": "dsfsdfsdfsdfs",
      "back": "sdfsdfsdfsdf",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 30
    },
    {
      "front": "werwerwerwerwer",
      "back": "wrwerwerwer",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 31
    },
    {
      "front": "ertert",
      "back": "ertertert",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 32
    },
    {
      "front": "sdfsdf",
      "back": "sdfsdf",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 33
    },
    {
      "front": "123",
      "back": "123",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 34
    },
    {
      "front": "3454564567",
      "back": "456745674567",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 35
    }
  ]
}